<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Conifer Software</title><link>https://conifersoftware.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Conifer Software</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 09:39:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://conifersoftware.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is Conifer?</title><link>https://conifersoftware.com/posts/what-is-conifer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 09:39:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://conifersoftware.com/posts/what-is-conifer/</guid><description>Conifer is an inventory management software platform made specifically for network marketing companies and their sellers. With conifer there are two facets: inventory management and point of sale.
With Conifer’s inventory management features sellers can add their existing inventory and then use that inventory to either sell directly to their clients or to transfer to another seller. This can be extremely useful as selling and transferring inventory are vital abilities which are not included within any other software platform.</description></item><item><title>Terms of Service</title><link>https://conifersoftware.com/termsofservice/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 12:26:44 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://conifersoftware.com/termsofservice/</guid><description>Effective as of 25 January 2020 Welcome to the Conifer Software&amp;nbsp;Terms of Use agreement. For purposes of this agreement, &amp;ldquo;Site&amp;rdquo; refers to the Company&amp;rsquo;s website, which can be accessed at https://conifersoftware.com&amp;nbsp;or through our mobile applications. &amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo; refers to the Company&amp;rsquo;s services accessed via the Site, in which users can &amp;nbsp;manage inventory, make transactions, and view past orders. The terms &amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;us,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo; refer to the Company. &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rdquo; refers to you, as a user of our Site or our Service.</description></item><item><title>Why You Need a Better Way to Sell doTERRA.</title><link>https://conifersoftware.com/posts/why-you-need-a-better-way-to-sell-doterra/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 09:39:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://conifersoftware.com/posts/why-you-need-a-better-way-to-sell-doterra/</guid><description>When you started your business selling doTERRA, you knew you were setting out on an adventure. Through all the ups and downs, you were determined to make it work. However, running your business has not come without its fair share of challenges, such as keeping track of orders, managing inventory levels, and trying to fill demand for out-of-stock products.
All of these are recurring issues that doTERRA sellers just like you face on a daily basis.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://conifersoftware.com/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 15:04:32 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://conifersoftware.com/privacy/</guid><description>Conifer Software, LLC built the Conifer POS app as a Commercial app. This service is provided by Conifer Software, LLC and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.
If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description></item><item><title>Error</title><link>https://conifersoftware.com/error/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 12:32:16 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://conifersoftware.com/error/</guid><description>Whoops! Looks like there was an error. Homepage</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://conifersoftware.com/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 10:21:54 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://conifersoftware.com/about/</guid><description>Conifer is a suite of software built specifically for Network Marketing consultants. Inventory Management Conifer allows you to manage your inventory with ease:
Adjust quantity and price of product variants Your inventory is automatically updated whenever you make a sale or transfer inventory. Conifer also allows you to manually adjust the quantity and price of products in your inventory. Transfer inventory between consultants Conifer makes transferring inventory between consultants easy.</description></item><item><title>Join The Waiting List</title><link>https://conifersoftware.com/join-waiting-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 09:56:59 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://conifersoftware.com/join-waiting-list/</guid><description> document.body.onload = function() { const urlParams = new URLSearchParams(window.location.search); let campaign = &#34;home&#34;; if (urlParams.get(&#34;campaign&#34;)) { campaign = urlParams.get(&#34;campaign&#34;) } document.getElementById(&#34;campaign&#34;).value = campaign; } Join the waiting list and get notified when Conifer is ready for your business.</description></item><item><title>Top 3 Problems with Network Marketing Software</title><link>https://conifersoftware.com/posts/top-three-problems-network-marketing-software/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 09:39:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://conifersoftware.com/posts/top-three-problems-network-marketing-software/</guid><description>As many Network Marketing consultants know, navigating the world of software for their business gets extremely hard, and is many times not very straight forward. There’s plenty of software that is provided by corporate under consultant fees, but many times this isn’t enough and requires the use of third party software. There is plenty of third party software out there built to run traditional businesses, but Network Marketing is anything but.</description></item><item><title>Added</title><link>https://conifersoftware.com/added/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 12:22:57 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://conifersoftware.com/added/</guid><description>All set! We&#39;ll notify you when there are progress updates! Check out our blog!</description></item></channel></rss>